

Contact

Phone

+421 904 566 248

Email

vorek994@gmial.com

Address

Čierne Vyšný koniec 994

Education

Stredná odborná škola strojnícka Kysucké Nové Mesto

2014 - 2018

Expertise

- HTML CSS JS
- React Boostrap
- Mechanist
- Crane Rigger
- Machine engineer

Language

Engl<u>ish</u>

Slovak

Jozef Vorek

Web Developer

About Me

My name is Jozef. I'm from Slovakia. I graduated from a technical high school with a focus on machinery. After finishing school, I worked as a machinist in the engineering industry. After two years, I left that job and started working as a load binder. In early 2023, I have decided to end my career as rigger and start carear as webdeveloper.

Experience

2018-2021

Schaeffler KNM

Mechanic adjuster

- Setting parameters of cnc machines
- Production of wheel bearings
- 2021-2023

Samoco S.R.O

Rigger

- Binding of high-tonnage loads
- Navigating the crane

2023

Learning Webdevelopment

• HTML CSS JS React Bootstrap Git